<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="#ffffff"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context=".TermsActivity">

    <ProgressBar
        android:visibility="gone"
        android:id="@+id/progressbar"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_centerVertical="true"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content" />

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical">
        <include
            android:id="@+id/toolbar"
            layout="@layout/toolbar" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/help"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:text="Terms &amp; Conditions"
            android:textColor="@color/myTextColor"
            android:textSize="24sp" />

        <ImageView
            android:id="@+id/imageView"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_gravity="center"
            app:srcCompat="@drawable/icon" />


        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="481dp">

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical">

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="match_parent"
                    android:layout_margin="10dp"
                    android:padding="5dp"
                    android:justificationMode="inter_word"
                    android:text="You agree to use, disclose, store, retain or otherwise process Personal Data solely for the purpose of performing under this Agreement. You shall maintain the accuracy and integrity of any Personal Data provided by us and in your possession, custody or control. You agree to retain Personal Data provided to you by us solely by using the software and tools provided by us. (“Personal Data”) means any information obtained in connection with this Agreement (i) relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; (ii) that can reasonably be used to identify or authenticate an individual, including but not limited to name, contact information, precise location information, persistent identifiers, and (iii) any information that may otherwise be considered “personal data” or “personal information” under the applicable law.
This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Netherlands without regard to its conflict of laws provisions. You hereby consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in the courts sitting in the Netherlands. Any and all notices permitted or required to be given hereunder shall be sent to the address first set forth on the Order Form, or such other address as may be provided, and deemed duly given (a) upon actual delivery, if delivery is by hand, (b) one (1) day after being sent by overnight courier, charges prepaid, or (c) by electronic mail to the designated recipient. In addition, you agree to receive autodialed calls or SMS messages sent by or on behalf of Company. The failure of either party to enforce, at any time or for any period of time, the provisions hereof, or the failure of either party to exercise any option herein, shall not be construed as a waiver of such provision or option and shall in no way affect that party’s right to enforce such provisions or exercise such option. Any modification or amendment to this Agreement shall be effective only if in writing and signed by both parties. In the event any provision of this Agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable by ruling of an arbitrator or court of competent jurisdiction, the remainder of this Agreement (and each of the remaining terms and conditions contained herein) shall remain in full force and effect. Any delay in or failure by either party in performance of this Agreement shall be excused if and to the extent such delay or failure is caused by occurrences beyond the control of the affected party including, but not limited to, decrees or restraints of Government, acts of God, strikes, work stoppage or other labor disturbances, war or sabotage (each being a “Force Majeure Event”). The affected party will promptly notify the other party upon becoming aware that any Force Majeure has occurred or is likely to occur and will use commercially reasonable efforts to minimize any resulting delay in or interference with the performance of its obligations under this Agreement. This Agreement may not be assigned, in whole or in part, by a party without the prior written consent of the other party, provided that each party may assign this agreement, upon notice to the other party, to (a) an affiliate of such party, or (b) in connection with the sale of all or substantially all of such party’s equity, business or assets. Subject to the foregoing, this Agreement shall be binding upon and shall inure to the benefit of each party hereto and its respective successors and assigns. Nothing in this Agreement shall be deemed to create any joint venture, joint enterprise, or agency relationship among the parties (except as specifically set forth in an Order Form), and no party shall have the right to enter into contracts on behalf of, to legally bind, to incur debt on behalf of, or to otherwise incur any liability or obligation on behalf of, the other party hereto, in the absence of a separate writing, executed by an authorized representative of the other party. Each party shall be solely responsible for its employees and contractors used in connection with this Agreement. This Agreement contains the full and complete understanding and agreement between the parties relating to the subject matter hereof and supersedes all prior and contemporary understandings and agreements, whether oral or written, relating such subject matter hereof. This Agreement may be executed in one or more counterparts and by exchange of electronically signed counterparts transmitted by pdf format, each of which shall be deemed an original and all of which, when taken together, shall constitute one and the same original instrument." />

            </LinearLayout>
        </ScrollView>


    </LinearLayout>

</RelativeLayout>